Guide to the Matt Kahn Papers SC1094 SC1094
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Personal
  - Photographs
    - Slides
      - Pt. Lobos Family, Apr-1966 (Box 12, Folder 93)
      - Puerta S. Maria/ Cadiz/ Sea/ Sky, Sep/ Oct - 1976 (Box 12, Folder 94)
      - Pugi, Dec-1966/ 67 (Box 12, Folder 95)
      - Quilt/ Fiskars, 37591 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Ravenna, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Red-Mix/ Handicap Symbol/ Central Concrete/ Hospital Bldg. Site, 36008 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Red bull car/ Flash light/ Squeezers/ Egg scale/ Gym balls, 38687 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Refinery, 31168 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Rejects - Matt Kahn, 34608 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Rel. Gothic, 32325 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Rel. Gothic, Jul-1986/ 88 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Rel. Gothic, 32325 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Rel. Gothic, 32325 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Rings (88), 32478 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Rings (pale slides), 32448 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Rigi/ Pilatus, 25781 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Rings (Bischoff/ Solomon), Jul-1961 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Rings (Moore/ Echaniz/ McGregor), Aug-1965 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Rite Offspring, 27426 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - River/ S. France, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Rietveld, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Roma, 1963/ 66/ 76 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Roma / Olympia/ Molfetta/ Firenze, 1977/ 80 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Roma '89, 32690 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Roma, Nov-1966 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - Roma + Tarquinia, 29160 (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - Rome (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - Rome (family), Nov-1966 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - Ronchamp, Jul-1966 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - Ronchamp Strasburg/ Swiss, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 27)
      - Roof, 35034 (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - Roofing/ Pompono Sand Fish/ Slinky, 32994 (Box 13, Folder 29)
      - Roses '91, 33420 (Box 13, Folder 30)
      - Roven, 32325 (Box 13, Folder 31)
      - Ryan Party, 31199 (Box 13, Folder 32)
      - S. Antimo/ S. Gimignano/ Galgano '89, 32690 (Box 13, Folder 33)
      - San Antimo/ Montalcino, 32325 (Box 13, Folder 34)
      - San Antonio, 26085 (Box 13, Folder 35)
      - San Francisco (Ira), 35977 (Box 13, Folder 36)
      - San Francisco - Arch, 1976-83 (Box 13, Folder 37)
      - San Francisco Bay Bridges, 1977-90 (Box 13, Folder 38)
      - S.F St. Mary's '03, 37742 (Box 13, Folder 39)
      - San Francisco Sions, 1998-2007 (Box 13, Folder 40)
      - San Gimignano '81, 29830 (Box 13, Folder 41)
      - San Gimignano/ Arezzo/ Siena/ Volterra/ Certaldo, 25659 (Box 13, Folder 42)
      - San Gregorio 2000-03, 36586 (Box 13, Folder 43)
      - San Quentin, Law School, Marin Civic Center/ Fedex, 37135 (Box 13, Folder 44)
      - Sapphire/ Giocomo/ L.A, 32874 (Box 13, Folder 45)
      - Santa Cruz - Sky rocket/ Roller Coaster, Jul-1969 (Box 13, Folder 46)
      - Sara, 32295 (Box 13, Folder 47)
      - Sara (1997-09), 35674 (Box 13, Folder 48)
      - Sard, 25781 (Box 13, Folder 49)
      - Sard #1, 25781 (Box 13, Folder 50)
      - Sard #2, 25781 (Box 13, Folder 51)
      - Santa Cruz, Mar-1967 (Box 13, Folder 52)
      - Scanno, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 53)
      - Scottish Festival, 36770 (Box 13, Folder 54)
      - Sculpture, 1959-66 (Box 13, Folder 55)
      - Segesta/ Erice/ Selinunte (Box 13, Folder 56)
      - Seiser Alm, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 57)
      - Selinunte/ Taormina/ L'Aquila/ Tarquinia/ Artimino, 30590 (Box 13, Folder 58)
      - Senta Nome, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 59)
      - Sermione, 25781 (Box 13, Folder 60)
      - S.Sepolcord/ Anghari, 32690 (Box 13, Folder 61)
      - Seq./ K.C/ Cycles/ Signs/ Taxi, 38108 (Box 13, Folder 62)
      - Seq./ K.C/ Water/ People, 38108 (Box 13, Folder 63)
      - Sequoia/ Rock, 38108 (Box 13, Folder 64)
      - Sequoia/ Valley, 37865 (Box 13, Folder 65)
      - Seville, 28004 (Box 13, Folder 66)
      - shamrock/ Daisies/ Rose leaves/ Jelly fish (commercial), 33664 (Box 13, Folder 67)
      - Shells/ Crystals, 26604 (Box 13, Folder 68)
      - Shidoni, 31291 (Box 13, Folder 69)
      - Sicilia, Feb-1963 (Box 13, Folder 70)
      - Sienna, 1962/ 66/ 79 (Box 13, Folder 71)
      - Sienna '81, 1981-87 (Box 13, Folder 72)
      - Sienna '88, 32325 (Box 13, Folder 73)
      - Sienna '89 Palio Related, 31594 (Box 13, Folder 74)
      - Sienna '89, 32690 (Box 13, Folder 75)
      - Siena, July-1986/87 (Box 13, Folder 76)
      - Sierra '80, 29434 (Box 13, Folder 77)
      - Sierra '82 Misc., 30195 (Box 13, Folder 78)
      - Sierra '82 (Vogelsang Camp Area), 30195 (Box 13, Folder 79)
      - Sierra '82 (Meadow/ Ireland/ waterfall), 30195 (Box 13, Folder 80)
      - Sierra '82 (Vogelsang Pass), 30195 (Box 13, Folder 81)
      - Sierra '82 (People), 30195 (Box 13, Folder 82)
      - Sierra Trip, 28703 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Simon Frazer Ferry (Lyda), 26512 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Siracusa (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Sitka Masks/ Alaska, Jul-1968 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Sitka Totem Park, Jul-1968 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Siusi, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Ski, Jan-1964 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Squaw Family High Camp (Aug '65), Aug-1965 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - St. Mary's Cathedral, 33055 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Southwest, 34547 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Southwest 1985, 31291 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Southwest Arches, 1985, 31291 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Southwest Personal, 31291 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Spa - PN/ Corona (Rend.), 26238 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Spain (Misc.), 1976-96 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Spoons/ Eggs/ St. Mary's, 36251 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - Spring '76/ Claire's slides of cats/ lilies/ orchids, 27881 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - Squaw '67 '68, Dec-1967 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - Squaw (Bill + Anne), Jan-1969 (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - Stadium Graduation '85, 31199 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Stamps/ De Young/ Lamp Posts, 39203 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Stanford Arch Supports, 33055 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - Stanford Cent. (Night), 31898 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - St. Antino/ Montalcino/ Impruneita/ Siena/ Milano/ Frankfort/ Orvieto, 35125 (Box 14, Folder 24)
      - St. Mary's SF, 28856 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - Stanford/ El Camino/ EZ2GET2, 1978/ 79 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - Steinberg/ RR Signs/ Claire/ Mask, 35674 (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - Stockholm/ Canterbury/ Southend, 1963/ 66/ 75 (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - Stockholm/ Sard/ Sitka/ Siena/ Tivo/ Trulli/ Torino, 1975 - 88 (Box 14, Folder 29)
      - Studio, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 30)
      - S.Vito/ Scarpa, 31959 (Box 14, Folder 31)
      - Sweden (Picasso)/ Stockholm, 29068 (Box 14, Folder 32)
      - Sweden/ Norway, 29068 (Box 14, Folder 33)
      - Swiss Post, Jan-1961 (Box 14, Folder 34)
      - Swimming Pool (1961), Jul-1961 (Box 14, Folder 35)
      - Sydney/ Australia, 28216 (Box 14, Folder 36)
      - Syntex (1974- 75), 27273 (Box 14, Folder 37)
      - Syntex Van Doren, 1974/ 75 (Box 14, Folder 38)
      - Tahoe (Scenic + Family) Lusic House/ Crystal Shores, Aug-1965 (Box 14, Folder 39)
      - Tahoe, Apr-1962 (Box 14, Folder 40)
      - Tahoe Siegels / WEYL visit '64, Dec-1967 (Box 14, Folder 41)
      - Tahoe Squaw/ Sierra Tahoe Hotel, Jan-1965 (Box 14, Folder 42)
      - Tahoe Skiing, Jan-1969 (Box 14, Folder 43)
      - Tahoe Squaw, 1965-1968 (Box 14, Folder 44)
      - Taj Mahal (Box 14, Folder 45)
      - Taos, 31291 (Box 14, Folder 46)
      - Tapestry, 1974-1978 (Box 14, Folder 47)
      - Tapestry, 1970-78 (Box 14, Folder 48)
      - Tapesry Dupes '67, Mar-1968 (Box 14, Folder 49)
      - Tattoo/ Masked Cars/ Earrings/ Spiral Redi-mix/ Credit cards, 36039 (Box 14, Folder 50)
      - T + C Village snowflakes (Box 14, Folder 51)
      - Teotihuacan, 26299 (Box 14, Folder 52)
      - Texas Nov 90 #1 #2, 33178 (Box 14, Folder 53)
      - Textiles, Aug-1966 (Box 14, Folder 54)
      - Timber Cove, 37135 (Box 14, Folder 55)
      - Timber Cove + Fort Ross (California) (Box 14, Folder 56)
      - Timber Cove/ Calif. coast/ Pacific coast/ Sea Ranch exit, Sep-1969 (Box 14, Folder 57)
      - Tivo, 1963/ 76 (Box 14, Folder 58)
      - Tivol/ Adria/ Ostia, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 59)
      - Tivol/ Abruzzi/ Scanno, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 60)
      - Toscana Trip, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 61)
      - Trani, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 62)
      - Trani/ Lecce/ Brindisi, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 63)
      - Trani, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 64)
      - Trulli, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 65)
      - Trulli/ Trani/ Troia/ Abruzzi (Box 14, Folder 66)
      - Trulli/ Luca, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 67)
      - Toulouse, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 68)
      - T-shirt/ Horse/ Pumpkin seeding/ Pink Succulent, 39448 (Box 14, Folder 69)
      - TUN, 29160 (Box 14, Folder 70)
      - TWA // NY 86, Feb-82/ Jul-86 (Box 14, Folder 71)
      - Type, 31168 (Box 14, Folder 72)
      - Tyrol, Dec-1966 (Box 14, Folder 73)
      - Urbino, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 74)
      - Ugly, 27515 (Box 14, Folder 75)
      - Urbino Ravenna, 1976/ 84 (Box 14, Folder 76)
      - Utah, 1995, 31168 (Box 14, Folder 77)
      - UXmas, 1972, 26299 (Box 14, Folder 78)
      - Valco, 1978-79, 1978/ 1979 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Valencia/ Taracona, 28004 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Vance Hanna - Body, 27242 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Vancouver, 26512 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Vehicles (Cement/ Aircraft/ Fire/ Dune), 26451 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Venice, 1976/ 79 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Venice, Aug-1963 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Venice (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Venice + Misc., 2002-2008 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Venice Verona '91, 33482 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Venice Biennale 1966, 1966 - 1975 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Venice Group Trip '91, 33482 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Venice/ Osalo/ Scarpa 1987, 31959 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Venice/ Casalle/ Metaponto/ Tarranto, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Venezia, 35247 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Verona, 1970/ 84 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Verona, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Viareggio, Mar-1963 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - Victoria/ Vancouver UBC, Jul-1968 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - Vicenza/ STRA/ Tiepolo, 33482 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - Vicenza, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - Vienna/ Koln/ Munich, Jul-1966 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      - Vienna Cathedral (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - Vietnam Memorial (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - Viterbo/ Montepulciano/ Orvieto, 1963/ 66/ 76 (Box 15, Folder 25)
      - Violin, 30742 (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - Volcano, 32782 (Box 15, Folder 27)
      - Washington Capitol, 30011 (Box 15, Folder 28)
      - Washington Monument/ Jefferson Memorial, 30011 (Box 15, Folder 29)
      - Watergate (Int) Toweri Lobbies/ Tile Construction, 26451 (Box 15, Folder 30)
      - Watts Towers '88, 32234 (Box 15, Folder 31)
      - Watts Towers '89, 32629 (Box 15, Folder 32)
      - Watts Towers 1991-03, 33359 (Box 15, Folder 33)
      - Watts '03, 37742 (Box 15, Folder 34)
      - Wats '05, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 35)
      - Watts '07, 39173 (Box 15, Folder 36)
      - Watts Towers + Basel Museum, 25781 (Box 15, Folder 37)
      - Watts Towers MOCA, 31898 (Box 15, Folder 38)
      - WET, 39873 (Box 15, Folder 39)
      - WET '03/ Misc. LA/ Magic Mountain, 37742 (Box 15, Folder 40)
      - WET (water show) (Box 15, Folder 41)
      - WET silicon graphics, 37012 (Box 15, Folder 42)
      - WEYL visit '83, 30376 (Box 15, Folder 43)
      - Windows Art, 28915 (Box 15, Folder 44)
      - Xmas 1992, 34335 (Box 15, Folder 45)
      - Xmas '93/ Mt. Aquarium/ Spider webs ('94), 34335 (Box 15, Folder 46)
      - Yacht Race, 1978, 28734 (Box 15, Folder 47)
      - Yacht Race II, 28734 (Box 15, Folder 48)
      - Yosemite (snow), Apr-1965 (Box 15, Folder 49)
      - Yosemite Nature (rainbow, snow, rocks, fall, lake), 1965/ 66 (Box 15, Folder 50)
      - Yosemite ('66), Apr-1966 (Box 15, Folder 51)
      - Yosemite (1966-68) (Box 15, Folder 52)
      - Yosemite ('68) IRA slalom, Feb-1968 (Box 15, Folder 53)
      - Yosemite ('68), Apr-1968 (Box 15, Folder 54)
      - Yosemite '86 Japanese Helmets, 31079 (Box 15, Folder 55)
      - Yosemite '86, 31444 (Box 15, Folder 56)
      - Yosemite/ Anne Dover Ferry, Apr-1966 (Box 15, Folder 57)
      - Yosemite/ Lyda/ POM/ Lynn, Apr-1968 (Box 15, Folder 58)
      - Yosemite/ Misc. Nature, 1968/ 1974 (Box 15, Folder 59)
      - Yosemite Sequoias/ Claire Easter "basket", 29677 (Box 15, Folder 60)
      - Yosemite with B + C, 27303 (Box 15, Folder 61)
      - Zermat, 1970/ 75 (Box 15, Folder 62)
      - Zermat/ Cervenia, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 63)
      - Zermat Flowers/ Lugano, 25781 (Box 15, Folder 64)
      - Zuni, 31291 (Box 15, Folder 65)
      - Zurich + Bern., 29830 (Box 15, Folder 66)
      - Zurich + Lucerne, 1965/ 69 (Box 15, Folder 67)
      - Unidentified, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 68)
      - Unidentified, 30590 (Box 15, Folder 69)
      - Unidentified, 33909 (Box 15, Folder 70)
      - Unidentified (Box 15, Folder 71)
      - Unidentified, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 72)
      - Unidentified, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 73)
      - Tapestry Dupes '67, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 74)
    - Southwest (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Stanford (Box 1, Folder 18)